Kheel, Theodore W. Speeches and Articles 6021/005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Excerpts of Remarks by Kheel New York Society of Security Analysts, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 57)
- NY Society of Security Analysts, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 58)
- Speeches & Articles National institute of Public Affairs, 1968-1970 (Box 15, Folder 59)
- Speeches & Articles WCBS-Newsmakers, 1968-1971 (Box 15, Folder 60)
- Speeches and Articles US Department of Labor, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 61)
- Legal Defense Fund Speeches and Articles, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 62)
- Queens College, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 63)
- New York Law Journal Speeches and Articles TWK, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 64)
- Speeches & Articles WCBS/TV Newsmakers, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  Aug 24
- Speeches & Articles WNBC - TV Searchlight, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 66)
- Vision 69, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 67)
- Harmonie Club, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Hatchet Encounter, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Hospital Executives Club, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Hebrew Home for the Aged, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Hugh Downs Presents, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Speeches & Articles international Association of Fire Chiefs, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Speeches and Articles Pennsylvania State University, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Speeches and Articles New Jersey Federation of Teachers, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Speeches and Articles New Jersey Library Trustees Association, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Speeches and Articles NJIMA, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Speeches and Articles Night Call, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Speeches and Articles United Parents Associations, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- United Presbyterian Church of Oxford, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- NY State Bar Association Young Lawyers Section, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Speeches and Articles National School Boards Association, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Speeches and Articles New York Board of Trade Inc., 1969 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Speeches and Articles Urban Mass Transportation, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Speeches and Articles Four Freedoms Award TWK, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Excerpts from Remarks of Kheel on Taylor Law, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Resolving Deadlocks in Public Employment, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  May 12
- Role of Legislative Bodies Under Taylor Law TWK, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  Sept 25
- Various Speeches on Mediation, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Speeches and Articles Labor Law and Practice, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Resolving Deadlocks in Public Employment, 1969-1973 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Hartwick College, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Southwestern Legal Foundation, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- LeMoyne College, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Minnesota Federation of Teachers, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Speeches and Articles Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Speeches and Articles WCBS/TV (Newsmakers), 1970 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Hotel Corporation of America, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Harcourt, Brace, and World, Inc., 1970 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Ford Foundation Conference on Blue Collar Alienation, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- US Army War College Speeches & Articles, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Speeches and Articles New Decade in Labor Relations What Changes We Should Expect In Public Employee Relations in the 1970s (Box 16, Folder 35)
- New Jersey Education Association Speeches and Articles (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Speeches and Articles New York City Council on Economic Education, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Speeches and Articles National Visual Communication Association, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Speeches and Articles The University of Georgia, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Speeches and Articles Public Employment Relations Board International Symposium, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- WPIX, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Principals of the New York City Board of Education, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  Jan 26
- Compulsory Arbitration in Public Sector Dispute Settlement Arvid Anderson, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- Mediation in Community Disputes Ronald Haughton, D'Jaris Watson, Gerald Cormick (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Why the $2.5 Billion Transportation Capital Facilities Bond Act must be Defeated, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 45)
- Bond Issue, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  Oct 20
- city Hall Agreement on Fare, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  Oct 21
- Speeches and Articles Executive Development Program of the Principals of the NYC Board of Education, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 48)
- Speeches and Articles League for Industrial Democracy, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 49)
- Speeches and Articles New School, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  Feb 24
- Speeches and Articles Cornell University, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 51)
- Harlem Youth Unlimited Economic Development Program, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 52)
- NYC Board of Education Principals Board of Mediation, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 53)
- Speeches and Articles WNBC - TV Newslight, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 54)
- Speeches and Articles WNBC - TV For Women only, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 55)
- Speeches and Articles Long Island University, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 56)
- Germany Conference 1972 Quality of Regional Development: The Case of NY The Quality of Regional Development: The Case of New York by TWK Germany Conference (Box 16, Folder 57)
- Quality of Regional Development: The Case of New York TWK Germany Conference, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 58)
- Emergency Disputes Legislation TWK Statement before US Senate, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 59)
- The Changes in Scope, Criteria and Techniques of Collective Bargaining La-Verne A. Rolle Summer, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 60)
- Nat'l Academy of Arbitrators, Atlanta, Georgia, April 5, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 61)
- Fort Worth Museum of Science and History, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 62)
- Foreign and Commonwealth Office, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 63)
- Establishing Grievance Procedures in Correctional Institutions, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  Nov 2
- WCBS-TV Citics in 176 R-1, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  Dec 11
- NYT TWK, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  April 7
- Productivity Speech, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 67)
- Ronald Reagan Presidential Conference at Hofstra University, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 68)
- Building Construction (Box 16, Folder 69)
- Special Inquiry on Public Employee Relations and the PERC in NJ Lewis B. Kaden (Box 16, Folder 70)
- Outline: How Collective Bargaining Works (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Kheel's Book Every Man's Guide to Labor (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Draft of Book TWK (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Collective Bargaining: What it can and cannot do TWK (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Preface to Book TWK (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Negotiation: The Process of Getting What You Want by Agreement TWK (Box 17, Folder 6)
- "Today's Man of Leisure" Esquire Study, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Kheel, Theodore W. "Report on Government Program Against Discrimination." Labor Report Bulletin Vol. 10 Aug 30, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- A Total Approach to Conflict Resolution, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Collective Bargaining Today Gerald Cormick, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Colleges are a Funny sort of Factory Lance Liebman, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- The Participants (Bookdraft), 1974 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Public Employee Union Book Draft TWK, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- The Strategy of Conflict Thomas C. Schelling, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Index, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Latest Drafts, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Application of Force, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Drafts TWK Ch. 1, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  Dec 3
- Drafts TWK Ch. 1, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  Nov 18
- What is Collective Bargaining, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  Dec 2
- Draft Ch. 2 - Criminal Conspiracy, civil Right, Mutual Obligation, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  Dec 23
- Book Project: Procedures Stamps of How Collective Bargaining Works, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  Sept 8
- Drafts - Kheel - Who are the Participants in Collective Bargaining Ch. 3, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  Jan 5
- Draft Ch. 1 TWK, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- The Strategies of Agreement Making TWK, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  Nov 15
- Drafts - Kheel Ch. 4 The Rules: Taut and Explicit, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Cartoons on Conflict Resolution The Cartoon Bank and TWK (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Course at Empire State College New York City, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Precis Re Meeting in Miami of Seminar on Collective Bargaining Unit Determinations Among Faculty in Higher Education (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Drafts of Report TWK (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Kheel on Transportation Vol. 11 1955-1972 Statements Press Releases (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Report of Findings and Recommendations to Mayor Robert F Wagner TWK, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Report on Government Program Against Discrimination TWK, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Removing Obstacles to Automation American Foundation on Automation and Employment, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  May 6-9
- the National Newspaper Industry the Economist Intelligence Unit, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Report to Speaker Anthony J. Travia on the Taylor Law TWK, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  Feb 21
- Facts about Fact-finding LMRS Bomstein, Tim, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Annual Report Office of Collective Bargaining NYC, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Final Report of the Assembly Advisory Council on Public Employee Relations Benjamin Aaron, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  May 15
- Report and Recommendations Commission on Academic Personnel Practice in CUNY, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- For Burson - Marsteller TWK, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Report and Determination in the Matter of Christo: The Gates Gordon J Davis, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Kheel The 4 horsemen of Conflict Resolution, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Summaries of Selected State Public Employee Labor Laws 21st Annual conference Association of Labor Mediation Agencies, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  June 25-30
- The Duty of Fair Representation An Overview Benjamin Aaron (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Strikes and Impasse Resolution in Public Employment Arvid Anderson (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Arzt, George "Kheel Strife of the Party" NY Post, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  Feb 13
- "An Early Orphan of the Journalistic Storms" Ken Auletta NY Daily News, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  April 18
- Browne Arthur Murdock Deal Ends Kheel Suit NY Daily News, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Clifford, Mark and Peter Howell Kheel-hauled Columbia Journalism Review, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Cockburn, Alexander Kheel, Murdoch, Watchdog" Voice, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Deitz, Roger M. The Keys to Conflict Resolution: Proven Methods of Resolving Disputes Voluntarily New York Law Journal, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  Aug. 13
- The Duty to Bargain Collectively During the Term of an Existing Agreement Archibald Cox and John T Dunlop (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Eckman, Fern Marja "A Peacemaker Meets the Press" New York Post, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Appraising the NYC Record: What Does it Tell Us About the Dimensions of the Problem Samuel M Ehrenhalt (Box 18, Folder 27)
- change and Challenge on the NY Scene: Charting the New Economic (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Economic and Demographic Change: The Call of NYC Samuel M. Ehrenhalt (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Friedman, Alexi. The Real Art of the Deal with mediator Theodore Kheel NYT, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Kheel Dropping Libel Suit Against Murdoch New York Times, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Gupte, Pranay. "Kheel answers questions on Carriage House Center on Global Issues." Earth Times, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  Jan 11
- Halbrook, Sherry. "Kheel: On Riding the Wave of Labor History." The Communicator, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Horwitz, Simi. "Theodore Kheel: America's Top Labor Mediator." West Side TV Shoppe and Restaurant Guide., 1988 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  March 26-April 1
- Israel, David "Kheel Comes out for the Big Shows." Washington Star, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Karp. Richard. "The Many Worlds of Theodore Kheel." New York, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  Jan 8
- Katcher, Edward "NY Strike-Settler No. 1" New York Posted Home News, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  June 2
- The Attack on Collective Bargaining TWK (Box 18, Folder 37)
- Can we Stand Strikes by Teachers, Police, Garbage Men, etc.? TWK (Box 18, Folder 38)
- Kheel Collective Bargaining and Community Disputes (Box 18, Folder 39)
- comments on Newspaper Negotiations TWK, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  Sept 1
- Corporate Communications in collective Bargaining TWK, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 41)
- Labor-Management Relations in industrial Society TWK (Box 18, Folder 42)
- Kheel A Labor Relations Policy, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 43)
- The Pros and Cons of Compulsory Arbitration, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 44)
- Kheel, Theodore w. How to Settle Vietnam (Box 18, Folder 45)
- Kheel, Theodore W. "What the War Labor Board Will Approve in Wage Incentives." Advanced Management Quarterly Journal Vol.9, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 46)
- Theodore Kheel's Answer." Letter New York, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 47)
- Why NY Magazine Refused to Accept My Ad, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 48)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Arbitrators: Blessed Damned? The Iron Age, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 49)
- Kheel Theodore W. "Umpires of 10,000 Labor Disputes." New York Times Magazine, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 50)
- Kheel, Theodore W. "Changing Patterns of Labor Relations in 1959." American Management Association Midwinter Personnel conference (Box 18, Folder 51)
- PEF Hires World-Class Contract Negotiator The Communicator, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 52)
- Professional Sports: Has Antitrust Killed the Goose that Card the Golden Egg? Koppett, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 53)
- Profile in Courage: Theodore W. Kheel" New York Chapter Arthritis Foundation, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  Sept
- Kheel, Theodore W. "Business and the Media" Cue New York, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 55)
- McCausland, Tim, "Thirtieth Annual homecoming at St Johns" The Forum St. John's School of Law, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  Jan 9
- Miller, James R. "The Solomon of city Hall." New York Herald Tribune, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 57)
- New York Magazine Kheel; Hip Operation "Replaceable You" Latham (Box 18, Folder 58)
- Marech, Rona. "Conflict Healer: At 81, Tea Kheel Still cools Tempers." Our Town, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 59)
- Medzon, Karyn Miller. "Can Kheel Calm Storm Shattering Daily News?" Riverdale Press, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 60)
- Mota, Gail. "Food for Legal Thought." NY Law Journal, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 61)
- Pinsley, Elliot. "Rico at its Worst: The Daily News has Picked the Wrong Weapon m the War with its Union." Manhattan Lawyer. Vol. 4, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  Jan-Feb
- Kenneth Rose The Duty of Fair Representation in Public Sector Collective Bargaining (Box 18, Folder 63)
- Rosenberg, John "Labor Doctor." PIC: The Magazine for Young Men.", 1948 (Box 18, Folder 64)
- Silverman, Francine. "Catching Up with Ted Kheel." Riverdale Review., 1996 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  Aug. 29
- Stead, Deborah. "Spreading the Gospel of Talking it Through." New York Times., 1999 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  May 9
- Strike Richard Vigilante Ch. 7 Acknowledgements, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 67)
- Wishlik. Debra. "The non-Broadcast TV Generation." East Side Express., 1984 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  July 25
- The YPO Metro "Negotiations Spell out Formulas For Success", 1975 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  Oct 16
- "Kheel's Suit Against Publisher Aftermath of 1978 Paper Strike." New York Law Journal, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 70)
- "Conflict Resolution - Or Agreement Making? An Interview with Theodore Kheel." Personnel., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  July-Aug
- "News Council Criticizes Murdoch." New York Times, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 72)
- "Kheel Advertisement Assails Post Publisher "Over a Critical Article." New York Times, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 73)
- "Kheel Sues Murdoch for 8M" NY Daily News; "Kheel Libel Suit Names Murdoch" NY Times, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 74)
- "Even Kheel?" (Letter to the Editor) Barron's, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  May 5
- (Sculpture Photo.) Labor chronicle Vol. 71, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 76)
- "How the Big Strikes are Settled." Reader's Digest, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 77)
- "Bricklayers' Wages are Fixed by Unusual Award.", 1948 (Box 18, Folder 78)
- "St. John's Affiliates with CNB-TV." (Box 18, Folder 79)
- Articles Concerning New York Profile (Box 18, Folder 80)
- "Low-Down on Wage Salaries with Kheel as High Man on the Totem Pole." (Box 18, Folder 81)
- Columbia University Seminars, 1978-1982 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Labor Relations in Government Seminar (Columbia Union), 1978 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Labor Relations in Government Seminar Columbia University, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Columbia University Labor Seminar - Collective Bargaining - Public Employee Union, 1967-1971 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Columbia University Seminar on Labor Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Columbia University - Teachers college, 1965-1971 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Empire State College State Univ. of NY 6587 Collective Bargaining Seminars, 1979-1981 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Empire state College Seminars 1-10 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Seminar - Empire State College First Session, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Seminar - Empire State College Second Session, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  Nov 6
- Seminar - empire State College third Session, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Seminar - Empire State College Fourth Session, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Seminar The Strategies and Tactics of Collective Bargaining, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- The Strategies and Tactics of Collective Bargaining Seminars 2,4,5,6 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Seminar The Strategies and Tactics of Collective Bargaining 1975 Related Materials (Box 20, Folder 15)
- The Strategies and Tactics of Collective Bargaining Seminar Ch. 3,8 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Strategies and Tactics of collective Bargaining Seminar - Fifth Session, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  Feb 6
- Strategies and Tactics of Collective Bargaining Seminar - session 6, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  May 6
- The Strategies and Tactics of Collective Bargaining Seminar 7 (The Mediator: Catalyst on a Hot Tine Roof) (Box 20, Folder 19)
- The Strategies and Tactics of Collective Bargaining Seminars 1-10 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Thomas, Evan (W.W. Norton and Co., Inc.), 1969 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Report on Theodore W. Kheel Manuscript Ed Townsend, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Labor Dispute Settlement ILR 684 Spring, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- McGeorge School of Law, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Seton Hall University (Speeches and Articles), 1967 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- (Draft) Collective Bargaining Speeches and Articles (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Speeches and Articles - Drafts - Collective Bargaining - Exploitation and Appl. Of Illegal Force (Walsh), 1981 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Speeches and Articles - Kheel Article Notes, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Foundation on Employee Health Medical Care and Welfare, Inc. Speeches & Articles, 1956-1958 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Labor Committees, house and Senate - Statement by Kheel et al., 1954 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- speeches and Articles - Natl. Urban League, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Urban of Greater NY, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Printing Industries and ITU Agreement Automation, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Speeches and Articles - Schelling,n.d., 1980 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Thomas Elbert, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- "They Call It A Game" - Bernie Parrish (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Sheppard Carroll "Working in the Twenty First Century" (Box 21, Folder 2)
- "Collective Bargaining Today", 1969 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- "Collective Bargaining Today" (Box 21, Folder 4)
- "Guide to Fair Employment Practices", 1964 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- "Lions in the street" - Paul Hoffman (Box 21, Folder 6)
- "Union Painters and Controlled Automation" Kelber and Schlesinger (Box 21, Folder 7)
- "Mike Quill Himself: A Memoir by Shirley Quill" (Box 21, Folder 8)
- "Transit and Arbitration A Decade of Decisions" TWK; "The Path to Transit Peace" J.K. Turcott (Box 21, Folder 9)
- "Report of the Mayor's Advisory Transit Committee to Honorable William O'Dwyer", 1946 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  Sept 9
- "Transit and Arbitration A Decade of Decisions" Theodore W. Kheel; "The Path to Transit Peace" J.K. Turcott (Box 22, Folder 1)
- "Transit and Arbitration A Decade of Decisions" Theodore W. Kheel; "The Path to Transit Peace" J.K. Turcott (Box 22, Folder 2)
- News Clippings Foundation on Employee Health Medical Care & Welfare, Inc.- American Foundation on Automation & Employment, Inc. (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Collective Bargaining, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Collective Bargaining, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees 5 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Collective Bargaining, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees 5 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Collective Bargaining, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees 6 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Collective Bargaining, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees 10 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Report on the Operations of the Office of Impartial Chairman, TWK, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  Nov 19
- Collective Bargaining, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees 1 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Collective Bargaining, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees 1 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Collective Bargaining, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees 3 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Collective Bargaining, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees 4 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Collective Bargaining, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees 7 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Collective Bargaining, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees 8 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Collective Bargaining, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees 9 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Collective Bargaining, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees 18 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Collective Bargaining, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees Tables, Index (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Pamplets, 1957-1978 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  1957, 1961-1963, 1971, 1975-1976, 1978
- Books for Ted Kheel, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  Tech Change Int'l Conference; The New Unionism; Tech Change Int'l conference; Reprinted from Personnel; Mediation and Arb. Of employment Disputes - John T. Dunlop
- Books for Ted, 2 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  The Rubber Workers; Homocracy CB: New Dimensions in Labor Relations; A. Philip Randolph A Biographical Portrait; CB Today
- Pamplets for Ted (Box 24, Folder 4)
  WI Law Review; Is the Strike Outmoded?; Is the Strike Outmoded?; Editor & Publisher; Editor & Publisher; A Generation's Report; Oridnary People Extraordinary Lives
- Commercial Arbitration at Its Best, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Managing Global Issues (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Nuclear Power Quick Reference II (Box 25, Folder 1)